<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on Shivam&#39;s Notes</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on Shivam&#39;s Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>09 May, 2024</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/all-posts/09-05-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/all-posts/09-05-24/</guid>
      <description>My setup worked twice today but I did not trade it. I think I chickened out because I was not sure for some reason idk why but yes I did not follow my rules today. In the later second half, out of fomo I tried to ride the wave but got caught right on the reversal and had to book a big loss. My few days win streak ended just because of my immaturity and carelessness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 middle class habits keeping you in rat race</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/naval_6_habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/naval_6_habits/</guid>
      <description>6 middle class habits keeping you in rat race # Link for yt video&#xA;1.Thinking that wealth is a zero sum game # (Change your mindset, its a positive sum game) All of wealth you see in society today was created by us at some point. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to make someone poor in order to be rich. Steve Jobs did not make Americans poorer when he launched Apple product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling temp, top_p and top_k</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/all-posts/controlling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/all-posts/controlling/</guid>
      <description>Controlling temp, top_p and top_k # So I have been working on a TTS model and for the last few days I am playing with few hyperparameters. In my specific use case, I found that temperature, top_p and top_k played a major role in audio generated.&#xA;temperature # helps control the randomness / creativity of the model. Basically you adjust the probabilities to force randomness or determinism. During training the temperature is 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Framework Thinking - How to think fast before you speak</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/framwork_thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/framwork_thinking/</guid>
      <description>Framework Thinking : How to think fast before you speak # Link for yt video&#xA;Steer not follow&#xA;Start from ground up. Think on the lines of first principles Always have some common framework ready in your brain library that are important to your field of work Learn how to connect different frameworks to gain deeper, more elaborate insights you can provide To be able to think fast - you need knowledge and framework both.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/llm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tech/llm/</guid>
      <description>my notes on LLM and anything related&#xA;Controlling top_p, top_k and temp </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade Diary</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/stock-market/diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/stock-market/diary/</guid>
      <description> My trading days # I post here only about my NSE index option trades.&#xA;May 9 </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
