<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shivam&#39;s Notes</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/docs/all-posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shivam&#39;s Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/docs/all-posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>09 May, 2024</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/all-posts/09-05-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/all-posts/09-05-24/</guid>
      <description>My setup worked twice today but I did not trade it. I think I chickened out because I was not sure for some reason idk why but yes I did not follow my rules today. In the later second half, out of fomo I tried to ride the wave but got caught right on the reversal and had to book a big loss. My few days win streak ended just because of my immaturity and carelessness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 May, 2024</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/all-posts/13-05-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/all-posts/13-05-24/</guid>
      <description>The market has been very volatile recently. I was able to ride the uptrend 3 times but due to the volatile nature of market (vix was around 21) I kept my ride short. But I was able to get the momentum in prices. The day ended in decent profit. Although I could have left a few positions running since the uptrend was very strong but considering the continuous red candles in BNF I told myself to be satisfied in short runs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling temp, top_p and top_k</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/all-posts/controlling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/all-posts/controlling/</guid>
      <description>Controlling temp, top_p and top_k # So I have been working on a TTS model and for the last few days I am playing with few hyperparameters. In my specific use case, I found that temperature, top_p and top_k played a major role in audio generated.&#xA;temperature # helps control the randomness / creativity of the model. Basically you adjust the probabilities to force randomness or determinism. During training the temperature is 1.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
