<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shivam&#39;s Notes</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shivam&#39;s Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>6 middle class habits keeping you in rat race</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/naval_6_habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/naval_6_habits/</guid>
      <description>6 middle class habits keeping you in rat race # Link for yt video&#xA;1.Thinking that wealth is a zero sum game # (Change your mindset, its a positive sum game) All of wealth you see in society today was created by us at some point. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to make someone poor in order to be rich. Steve Jobs did not make Americans poorer when he launched Apple product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Competition is for losers</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/competition/</guid>
      <description>Competition is for Losers # Link for yt video&#xA;1. Creating value # A business creates X dollars of value and capture Y% of X. (both x and y are independent) To capture value you need to capture X and Y both&#xA;2. Perfect competition # Pros&#xA;easy to model efficient in a static world politically stable Cons&#xA;psychologically unhealthy irrelevant in a dynamic world preempts question of value 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Framework Thinking - How to think fast before you speak</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/framwork_thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/framwork_thinking/</guid>
      <description>Framework Thinking : How to think fast before you speak # Link for yt video&#xA;Steer not follow.&#xA;1. Learn to think # Start from ground up. Think on the lines of first principles&#xA;2. Have a go to plan # Always have some common framework ready in your brain library that are important to your field of work&#xA;3. Connect the dots # Learn how to connect different frameworks to gain deeper, more elaborate insights you can provide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Asked a $15BN Investor for Life Advice</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/billionaire_advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/billionaire_advice/</guid>
      <description>I Asked a $15BN Investor for Life Advice # Link for yt video&#xA;Investor&amp;rsquo;s Advice and Background: The interviewee, a $15 billion investor, shares life advice based on personal experiences. He emphasizes the importance of learning from mistakes, citing a personal history of losing money on five of his first eight deals. The investor highlights the need for patience in career pursuits, suggesting a 10-year timeline for success. Habits and Success: Success, according to the investor, is a result of consistent, small habits rather than grand, sweeping moves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why you are not consistent ?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/inconsistent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/general-muse/inconsistent/</guid>
      <description>Why you are not consistent ? # Link for yt video&#xA;Existential overwhelm : You start to think that there are n number of things i could be doing so what I am doing now is it good enough ? is it attractive looking ? does it have any meaning ? you start to think this is worthless and i am not gonna do it in long term so why bother putting in efforts now.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
